Finding aid to the Margaret Mahoney papers SSC.MS.00230
Sophia Smith Collection
- Subject files, 1961-2007; 7; 1.5 linear feet (4 boxes)
  - People, Carnegie Days, 1999-2007 (Box 67, Folder 30-33)
  - People, Commonwealth Fund people, 1984-2005 (Box 68, Folder 1-3)
  - People, Karen Davis talk, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - People, Family, 1998-2005 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - People, Barbara Finberg, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 6-8)
  - People, Friends, 1996-2008 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - People, Ted Katz, Institute of American Indian Arts, 1972-1974 (Box 68, Folder 10-12)
  - People, Mary Kohler memorial, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - People, Kenneth Lash, 1973-1975 (Box 68, Folder 14-15)
  - People, Myrna Loy will, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - People, Rene Maheu (UNESCO), 1963-1976 (Box 68, Folder 17-19)
  - People, Medicine, 1998-2004 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - People, Miscellaneous, 1987-2006 (Box 68, Folder 21-23)
  - People, New York City, 1999-2005 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - People, Obituaries, 1988-1993 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - People, "People", 1993-2008 (Box 69, Folder 3-6)
  - People, RWJF [Robert Wood Johnson Foundation] Days, 1988-2006 (Box 69, Folder 7-9)
  - People, Franklin Delano Roosevelt, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - People, Sixties, 1992-2008 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - People, Brant Sloan, 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 12-14)
  - People, Edward Staempfli, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - People, State Department Days, Helen Rowan, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 16-17)
  - People, State Department Days, Women, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 18-21)
  - Personal improvement or career planning, 1974-1991 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Philanthropy: Environment in which it has to function, 1993-1998 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Philanthropy: Environment in which it has to function, 1993-1998 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Quotes, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Research on issue of role and responsibility of trustees, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Tennessee history, 1995-2003 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Untitled, 1991-2002 (Box 70, Folder 5-10)
  - Art Workers Newsletter, Vol 2 No 4-5, 1971-1989 (Mapcase 52, Folder 1)
  - Clinical Trends in Ophthalmology, Otolaryngology, Allergy Vol. 10, No. 7, 1972; 1 items (Mapcase 52, Folder 1)
  - "The Deeper Meaning of Apollo 17," New York Times, 1 Jan 1973 (Mapcase 52, Folder 1)
  - "Excerpts from Nobel Lecture by Solzhenitsyn," New York Times, 25 Aug 1972 (Mapcase 52, Folder 1)
  - Allan Kaprow posters, Four Happenings and EAT, 1964 (Mapcase 52, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth Fund People: "DNA Heroes, Long Unsung," Newsday, 2 Mar 2003 (Mapcase 52, Folder 1)
- Restricted materials, 1925-2002; 8; 0.5 linear feet (1 box)
  Restricted materials include medical information for Margaret E. Mahoney and material related to Board nominations. This material will be open in 2062.
  - Board Nominations, 1980-1989; 4 folders (Box 72, Folder 1-4)
  - Health record and insurance claims, 1925-1986; 12 folders (Box 72, Folder 5-8, Box 73, Folder 1-4)
  - Priscilla Van de Workeen, 1982-1984; 1 folders (Box 73, Folder 5)